

·-

+6281263798717

delimasihombing92@gmail.com



Komplek alvita jalan rajawali blok n no 14a Tangerang

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF MANAJEMENT STIE TRIBUANA | 2018

SMA MARIA GORETTI | 2019

#### SKILSS

- Strong Sales Professional
- Customer Oriented
- Microsoft Office
- Risk & Complain Management
- Customer Service
- Communication

#### **INTEREST**

- Internet (Browsing, Media sosial)
- Listen Music
- Reading

#### **LANGUAGE**

- O BAHASA INDONESIA
- ENGLISH

# DELIMAN SIHOMBING

## BANCASSURANCE LIFE CONSULTANT

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced 5 years in financial & insurance Industry and 3 years in perbankan. Im a fast learner, highly motivated person who has good analytical, creative thinking, and problem solving ability to develop new ideas and enhance existing knowledge/skill.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### PT. AIA FINANCIAL

#### Bancassurance Life Consultant | FROM APRIL 2017 - Present

Establish and maintain good business relationships with bank partner, customers and providing consultation on protection planning and customer financial goals. Ensure all business processes run according to company standard procedures. Assist in processing customer claims.

## Bank CENTRAL ASIA (BCA)

Customer Service Officer | FROM 2014 - APRIL 2017

Checking & ensuring the correctness and completeness of requirements for account opening.

Manages client due diligence visit and service review call.

Build trusted partnerships with customer at the daily service.

Crosselling (banking product, KPR, KKB, KSM, AIA)

Handling complaint.

#### PT. GLOBALBEAUTY

Customer Service Officer | FROM 2010 - 2014

Set client treatment schedule.

Create invoices.